[{"__v": 0, "_id": "59b010d54a9c7f202d2e0581", "answers": [{"answer": "serious", "id": "VTbUV", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "minor", "id": "3VDwY", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "high", "id": "nQOEP", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "severe", "id": "kMGw4", "type": "editor"}], "created_at": "2017-09-06T15:14:29.599Z", "has_suggest_answer": true, "id": "59b010d54a9c7f202d2e0581", "question": "A ………. pain", "type": "multiple_choose", "updated_at": "2017-09-06T15:21:05.092Z"}, {"__v": 0, "_id": "59b010d54a9c7f202d2e0583", "answers": [{"answer": "serious", "id": "ywuav", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "minor", "id": "TWu60", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "high", "id": "37DMl", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "severe", "id": "VO1zC", "type": "editor"}], "created_at": "2017-09-06T15:14:29.616Z", "has_suggest_answer": true, "id": "59b010d54a9c7f202d2e0583", "question": "………… injuries", "type": "multiple_choose", "updated_at": "2017-09-06T15:21:05.122Z"}, {"__v": 0, "_id": "59b010d54a9c7f202d2e0585", "answers": [{"answer": "serious", "id": "zwko4", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "minor", "id": "WCzLP", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "high", "id": "4xTzE", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "severe", "id": "F9xko", "type": "editor"}], "created_at": "2017-09-06T15:14:29.625Z", "has_suggest_answer": true, "id": "59b010d54a9c7f202d2e0585", "question": "a ………… illness", "type": "multiple_choose", "updated_at": "2017-09-06T15:21:05.133Z"}, {"__v": 0, "_id": "59b010d54a9c7f202d2e0587", "answers": [{"answer": "serious", "id": "Ptmmw", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "minor", "id": "nBbIb", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": {"blocks": [{"depth": 0, "entityRanges": [], "inlineStyleRanges": [], "key": "95t4b", "text": "low", "type": "unstyled"}]}, "id": "9zfVU", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": {"blocks": [{"depth": 0, "entityRanges": [], "inlineStyleRanges": [], "key": "8lnd8", "text": "severe", "type": "unstyled"}]}, "id": "1GL8L", "type": "editor"}], "created_at": "2017-09-06T15:14:29.629Z", "has_suggest_answer": true, "id": "59b010d54a9c7f202d2e0587", "question": "a ……….. temperature", "type": "multiple_choose", "updated_at": "2017-09-06T15:21:05.140Z"}, {"__v": 0, "_id": "59b010d54a9c7f202d2e0589", "answers": [{"answer": "serious", "id": "m6dA8", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "minor", "id": "0JLnA", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "high", "id": "qmWsT", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "severe", "id": "YDy5l", "type": "editor"}], "created_at": "2017-09-06T15:14:29.633Z", "has_suggest_answer": true, "id": "59b010d54a9c7f202d2e0589", "question": "a ……….. fever", "type": "multiple_choose", "updated_at": "2017-09-06T15:21:05.153Z"}, {"__v": 0, "_id": "59b010d54a9c7f202d2e058b", "answers": [{"answer": "get", "id": "w6YIP", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "take", "id": "6bjlE", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "have", "id": "uK708", "type": "editor"}], "created_at": "2017-09-06T15:14:29.637Z", "has_suggest_answer": true, "id": "59b010d54a9c7f202d2e058b", "question": "I’ll just put this thermometer under your tongue and ……………… your temperature now.", "type": "multiple_choose", "updated_at": "2017-09-06T15:21:05.160Z"}, {"__v": 0, "_id": "59b010d54a9c7f202d2e058d", "answers": [{"answer": "got", "id": "KcEVU", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "took", "id": "hjjeg", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "had", "id": "EMCp3", "type": "editor"}], "created_at": "2017-09-06T15:14:29.641Z", "has_suggest_answer": true, "id": "59b010d54a9c7f202d2e058d", "question": "She ………. a nasty accident falling off a ladder last week.", "type": "multiple_choose", "updated_at": "2017-09-06T15:21:05.166Z"}, {"__v": 0, "_id": "59b010d54a9c7f202d2e058f", "answers": [{"answer": "get/take", "id": "im9fJ", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "take/take", "id": "Yu3qa", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "have/get", "id": "LpVU5", "type": "editor"}], "created_at": "2017-09-06T15:14:29.646Z", "has_suggest_answer": true, "id": "59b010d54a9c7f202d2e058f", "question": "Do you often ………. out of breath when you ………… exercise?", "type": "multiple_choose", "updated_at": "2017-09-06T15:21:05.173Z"}, {"__v": 0, "_id": "59b010d54a9c7f202d2e0591", "answers": [{"answer": "Getting/taking", "id": "hBDOt", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "Taking/getting", "id": "ilP97", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "Having/getting", "id": "tNYQb", "type": "editor"}], "created_at": "2017-09-06T15:14:29.652Z", "has_suggest_answer": true, "id": "59b010d54a9c7f202d2e0591", "question": "I’ve been ………. these pills for three weeks now, and I don’t seem to be ……… better.", "type": "multiple_choose", "updated_at": "2017-09-06T15:21:05.181Z"}, {"__v": 0, "_id": "59b010d54a9c7f202d2e0593", "answers": [{"answer": "got", "id": "mtT86", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "took", "id": "PtTlb", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "had", "id": "FZXIh", "type": "editor"}], "created_at": "2017-09-06T15:14:29.657Z", "has_suggest_answer": true, "id": "59b010d54a9c7f202d2e0593", "question": "She’s in great shape and she ……………. a baby just two months ago.", "type": "multiple_choose", "updated_at": "2017-09-06T15:21:05.188Z"}, {"__v": 0, "_id": "59b010d54a9c7f202d2e0595", "answers": [{"answer": "get", "id": "qWZJr", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "take", "id": "DLHB8", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "have", "id": "A7UqO", "type": "editor"}], "created_at": "2017-09-06T15:14:29.661Z", "has_suggest_answer": true, "id": "59b010d54a9c7f202d2e0595", "question": "Please roll up your sleeve so that I can ………… your blood pressure.", "type": "multiple_choose", "updated_at": "2017-09-06T15:21:05.194Z"}, {"__v": 0, "_id": "59b010d54a9c7f202d2e0597", "answers": [{"answer": "get", "id": "w0tiI", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "take", "id": "Oea33", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "have", "id": "wHhb8", "type": "editor"}], "created_at": "2017-09-06T15:14:29.666Z", "has_suggest_answer": true, "id": "59b010d54a9c7f202d2e0597", "question": "I’ve been going to the gym recently because I’m trying to ………….. in shape for running the marathon next spring.", "type": "multiple_choose", "updated_at": "2017-09-06T15:21:05.200Z"}, {"__v": 0, "_id": "59b010d54a9c7f202d2e0599", "answers": [{"answer": "get / had", "id": "SpVrM", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "take/had", "id": "7kfb5", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "have/ have", "id": "MsNGu", "type": "editor"}], "created_at": "2017-09-06T15:14:29.670Z", "has_suggest_answer": true, "id": "59b010d54a9c7f202d2e0599", "question": "I had to ………………. some time off work because I ………… an operation on my knee.", "type": "multiple_choose", "updated_at": "2017-09-06T15:21:05.207Z"}]